Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Visual Materials, 1962-2009
  - Subseries 3: Moving Images, 1965-2000
    - Russia 24A Kalinin performance (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 5)
    - Russia 25A (21 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 6)
    - Russia 26A (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 7)
    - Russia 27A (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 8)
    - Russia 28A (21 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 9)
    - Russia C4 Kalinin rehearsal (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 10)
    - Russia C5 Kalinin rehearsal (17 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 11)
    - Russia C6 Kalinin rehearsal (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 12)
    - Kalinin Performance Tape C-7 004 (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam SP (Box 134, Item 13)
    - Kalinin Performance Tape C-8 005 (21 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam SP (Box 134, Item 14)
    - Russia C9 Kalinin performance (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 15)
    - Russia C10 Kalinin performance (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 16)
    - Russia C11 Kalinin performance (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 17)
    - Russia C12 Kalinin performance (18 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 18)
    - Russia Kalinin performance B-cam coverage of C-machine tape changes 1 of 3 (13 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 19)
    - Russia Kalinin performance closing ceremony B-camera 3 of 3 (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 20)
    - Russia Kalinin performance B machine coverage of C machine tape changes (20 minutes), 1988 June 12; Betacam (Box 134, Item 21)
    - Russia A29 Kalinin daycare (20 minutes), 1988 June 13; Betacam (Box 134, Item 22)
    - Russia A30 Kalinin daycare, children’s dance (18 minutes), 1988 June 13; Betacam (Box 135, Item 1)
    - Russia Kalinin A31 daycare and interviews (20 minutes), June 13, 1988; Betacam (Box 135, Item 2)
    - Russia Kalinin B21 Pioneer Palace (20 minutes), June 13, 1988; Betacam (Box 135, Item 3)
    - Russia Kalinin 22 Pioneer Palace (20 minutes), 1988 June 13; Betacam (Box 135, Item 4)
    - Russia Kalinin 24 Pioneer Palace GMA stuff (20 minutes), 1988 June 13; Betacam (Box 135, Item 5)
    - Russia arrive in Moscow (13 minutes), 1988 June 14; Betacam (Box 135, Item 6)
    - Russia 25 Special performance and Post-show interviews (21 minutes), 1988 June 14; Betacam (Box 135, Item 7)
    - Russia 26 Interviews in Kalinin, host families at hotel (14 minutes), 1988 June 14; Betacam (Box 135, Item 8)
    - Russia Moscow peace foundation (18 minutes), 1988 June 18; Betacam (Box 135, Item 9)
    - Russia A-Camera, Moscow (20 minutes), 1988 June 19; Betacam (Box 135, Item 10)
    - Russia UWP in USSR, offline working copy (48 minutes), circa 1988; 3/4” Umatic (Box 135, Item 11)
    - Cast C Philadelphia Phillies Pregame (23 minutes), 1988 June; 3/4” Umatic (Box 135, Item 12)
    - Sydney, Grand Finale (31 minutes), 1988 August; VHS PAL (Box 135, Item 13)
    - Highlights video Southern Bell sponsorship (45 minutes), 1988 September; 3/4” Umatic (Box 135, Item 14)
    - EXPO 88 Brisbane Australia Cast E at River Stage (100 minutes), 1988; 1/2” PAL VHS (Box 135, Item 15)
    - Timmy’s Telethon (19 minutes), 1988; 1/2” VHS (Box 135, Item 16)
    - Cast C AVRO-TV special, Netherlands (61 minutes), 1989 April 13; 3/4” Umatic PAL (Box 135, Item 17)
    - Final Combined Safety: 1) TV Spots, 2) Face to Face, Reel #2 (18 minutes), 1989 June 9; 3/4” Umatic (Box 135, Item 18)
    - Master, 1A (60 minutes), 1989 July 21; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 1)
    - Monday, Blue/Y, Reel 1 (60 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 2)
    - Monday, Blue/Y, Reel 3 (48 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 3)
    - Monday, Blue/Y, Reel 4 (60 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 4)
    - Monday, Blue/Y, Reel 5 (21 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 5)
    - Monday, Red X, Reel 1 (60 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 6)
    - Monday, Red X, Reel 2 (60 minutes), 1989 July 24; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 136, Item 7)
    - Coca Cola & UWP Cast E Oslo (8 minutes), 1989; VHS Videotape (Box 137, Item 1)
    - Russia (63 minutes), 1989; 1/2” VHS (Box 137, Item 2)
    - Video Album, Face to Face #8261 (50 minutes), 1989; 1/2” VHS (Box 137, Item 3)
    - Fort Slocum #2 telecine from film, marginal video RF level (21 minutes), 1990 January 2; 3/4” Umatic (Box 137, Item 4)
    - Leningrad Tallinn Cast B (11 minutes), 1990 March 21-30; Betacam SP (Box 137, Item 5)
    - Poland (100 minutes), 1990 March 21-30; 1/2” VHS (Box 137, Item 6)
    - La Paloma Tape #3 of 6 (16 minutes), 1990 May 30; Betacam SP (Box 137, Item 7)
    - La Paloma Tape #4 of 6 (20 minutes), 1990 May 30; Betacam SP (Box 137, Item 8)
    - La Paloma Tape #6 of 6 (22 minutes), 1990 May 30; Betacam SP (Box 137, Item 9)
    - 25th Anniversary, Opening Ceremony 3A, Denver, Colorado (86 minutes), 1990 July 25-29; 1” Type C videotape (Box 138, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary, Opening Ceremony 3B, Denver, Colorado (96 minutes), 1990 July 25-29; 1” Type C videotape (Box 138, Item 2)
    - Silver Celebration Denver Video Album (118 minutes), 1990 July 25-29; 1/2” VHS (Box 138, Item 3)
    - Silver Celebration KUSA-TV (28 minutes), 1990 July 27; 3/4” Umatic (Box 138, Item 4)
    - Historic Video (35 minutes), 1990 August 21; 1/2” VHS (Box 138, Item 5)
    - Denver, We are many, We Are One, (120 minutes), 1990 September 5; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 139, Item 1)
    - Denver Silver Anniversary Celebration (120 minutes), 1990 August 10; 1” Type C Videocassette (Box 140, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary- Opening Ceremony, 4D yellow program rec (63 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 141, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 6A red (65 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 141, Item 2)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 6B green iso machine (65 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type videotape (Box 141, Item 3)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 6C blue iso machine (65 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 142, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 9A red iso machine (93 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 142, Item 2)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 9D program (96 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 142, Item 3)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 10A 2nd half (96 minutes), 1990 July; 1” Type C videotape (Box 142, Item 4)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 12B 1st half (90 minutes), 1990 July; 1” Type C videotape (Box 143, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 12D 1st half program (96 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 143, Item 2)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 13A last part (35 minutes), 1990 July; 1” Type C videotape (Box 143, Item 3)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 13B, program (35 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 143, Item 4)
    - 25th Anniversary evening show (finale event) 13D, program (44 minutes), 1990 July 27; 1” Type C videotape (Box 144, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 1A, Denver, Colorado (51 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 144, Item 2)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 1B, Denver, Colorado (40 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 144, Item 3)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 1C, Denver, Colorado (38 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 144, Item 4)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 1D, Denver, Colorado (47 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 145, Item 1)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 2A, Denver, Colorado (47 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 145, Item 2)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 2B, Denver, Colorado (84 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 145, Item 3)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 2C, Denver, Colorado (84 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 145, Item 4)
    - 25th Anniversary, Black Tie Gala 2D, Denver, Colorado (84 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 145, Item 5)
    - Global Forum 7A (95 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 146, Item 1)
    - Global Forum 7B (92 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 146, Item 2)
    - Global Forum 7C (95 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 146, Item 3)
    - Global Forum 7D, switched program tape (72 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 146, Item 4)
    - Global Forum 8A (43 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 147, Item 1)
    - Global Forum 8B (46 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 147, Item 2)
    - Global Forum 8C (43 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 147, Item 3)
    - Global Forum 8D (76 minutes), 1990; 1” Type C videotape (Box 147, Item 4)
    - Lute Olson & Bill Frieder for Up with People benefit (8 minutes), 1991 April 21; Betacam SP (Box 148, Item 1)
    - Windows Reels 1-5 (112 minutes), 1991 September; 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 2)
    - Windows Reels 6 & 7 (51 minutes), 1991 September; 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 3)
    - Windows Reels 8 & 9 (49 minutes), 1991 September; 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 4)
    - Windows Reels 15-20 (120 minutes), 1991 September; 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 5)
    - Toyota 1992, #384 (English Version) (12 minutes), 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 6)
    - UWP Show Tucson (12 minutes), 1992; 1/2” VHS (Box 148, Item 7)
    - World in Motion Dress Rehearsal, Reel #1 (61 minutes), 1993 February 13; 3/4” Umatic (Box 148, Item 8)
    - World in Motion Dress Rehearsal, Reel #2 (57 minutes), 1993 February 13; 3/4” Umatic (Box 148, Item 9)
    - World in Motion Video Album (73 minutes), 1993; 1/2” PAL VHS (Box 148, Item 10)
    - Promo Spencer Christian (3.5 minutes), 1993 February 23; 1” Type C Videotape (Box 148, Item 11)
    - World in Motion 1A (80 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 149, Item 1)
    - World in Motion 3A (84 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 149, Item 2)
    - World in Motion 5A (78 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 149, Item 3)
    - World in Motion 7A (90 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 149, Item 4)
    - World in Motion 7B (90 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 149, Item 5)
    - World in Motion 9A (75 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 150, Item 1)
    - World in Motion 9B (79 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 150, Item 2)
    - World in Motion 11A (77 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 150, Item 3)
    - World in Motion 11B (78 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 150, Item 4)
    - World in Motion Tape 13A (71 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 151, Item 1)
    - World in Motion 13B (73 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 151, Item 2)
    - World in Motion Tape 15A (85 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 151, Item 3)
    - World in Motion 15B (85 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 151, Item 4)
    - World in Motion 17A (23 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 152, Item 1)
    - World in Motion 17B (23 minutes), 1993 June 8; 1” Type C videotape (Box 152, Item 2)
    - Dedication Celebration (11 minutes), 1993 July 22-23; 1/2” VHS (Box 152, Item 3)
    - Up with People: Papal Welcome- Pope John Paul II Mile High Stadium- Denver, Colorado (34 minutes), 1993 August 12; 1/2” VHS (Box 152, Item 4)
    - Project Pride, Version Two (8 minutes), 1993; 1/2” VHS (Box 152, Item 5)
    - History & Highlights of 1994 Show (16 minutes), 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 1)
    - Make a Wish Foundation PSAs (3 minutes), 1994; 3/4” Umatic (Box 153, Item 2)
    - El Pomar Awards Presentation (63 minutes), 1996 November 22; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 3)
    - Defective Tape- Premiere Performance Cast E (60 minutes), 1996; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 4)
    - El Pomar Foundation 1997 Awards program (59 minutes), 1997 November 21; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 5)
    - NASA Apollo XVII (17 minutes), 1998 January 5; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 6)
    - UWP Pre-Show Video (9 minutes), 1998 February; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 7)
    - Dr. Toyoda Visit (17 minutes), 1998 April 8; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 8)
    - NATO Reel 1 (34 minutes), 1998 April 24; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 9)
    - NATO Reel 2 (33 minutes), 1998 April 24; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 10)
    - UWP in Eastern Europe (12 minutes), 1998 January 19; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 11)
    - Casting Registration (68 minutes), 1998 July 19; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 12)
    - Opening Session (75 minutes), 1998 July 20; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 13)
    - El Pomar Awards (59 minutes), 1998; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 14)
    - Performance in St. Peters Square (48 minutes), 1998; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 15)
    - Stockholm (20 minutes), 1998; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 16)
    - Stockholm footage School Project 1998 Raw (146 minutes), 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 17)
    - UWP in East Europe (12 minutes), 1998; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 18)
    - Celebration of Peace, Gen Colin L. Powell (56 minutes), 1999 May 12; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 19)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #1 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 153, Item 20)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #1 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 153, Item 21)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #2 (27 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 1)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #2 (28 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 2)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #3 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 3)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #3 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 4)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #4 (35 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 5)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #4 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 6)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #5 (21 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 7)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #5 (21 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 8)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #6 (37 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 9)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #6 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 10)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #7 (25 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 11)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #7 (25 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 12)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #8 (36 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 13)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #8 (35 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 14)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #9 (9 minutes), 1999 May 27; Betacam SP (Box 154, Item 15)
    - Viva la Gente Tape #9 (9 minutes), 1999 May 27; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 16)
    - Lynn Morris Appreciation Banquet (152 minutes), 1999 June 19; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 17)
    - Dedication Ceremony of the Wesley and Suzanne Dixon Int’l HQ (12 minutes), 1999 July; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 18)
    - 73rd Americas Thanksgiving Parade- Live from Detroit (120 minutes), 1999; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 19)
    - Staff Cast D Cast Appreciation (14 minutes), 1999; 1/2” VHS (Box 154, Item 20)
    - “Deutschlandsburg Cast A (2 minutes), 1999-2000; 3/4” Umatic (Box 155, Item 1)
    - Opening Session Comments & Candids (10 minutes), 2000 January; 1/2” VHS (Box 155, Item 2)
    - Cast C Arhus Denmark (38 minutes), 2000 April 28; Betacam SP (Box 155, Item 3)
    - Cast C Arhus, Denmark Host Family Conclusion Tape 4 #147808 (7 minutes), 2000; Betacam SP (Box 155, Item 4)
    - Cast C Arhus, Denmark Host Family Footage Tape 3 #134917 (34 minutes), 2000; Betacam SP (Box 155, Item 5)
    - Cast C Arhus, Denmark Tape 1 #131746 (30 minutes), 2000; Betacam SP PAL (Box 155, Item 6)
    - Cast C Arhus, Denmark #147201 Misc. locations (36 minutes), 2000; Betacam SP (Box 155, Item 7)
    - Cast C Arhus, Denmark #162975 (36 minutes), 2000; Betacam SP PAL (Box 155, Item 8)
    - Legacy (33 minutes), 2000 July; 1/2” VHS (Box 155, Item 9)
    - New Horizons (4 minutes), 2000 July; 1/2” VHS (Box 155, Item 10)
    - Backstage Prep ETC, Negative (Silent) (21 minutes: 756 feet), undated; 16mm color negative (Box 155, Item 11)
    - “Bear Creek Ranch” (11 minutes: 384 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 155, Item 12)
    - “Bob Banner 1024EF92 Test 1-2”, 16mm silent color, original camera film (30 minutes), undated; 16mm silent motion picture film (Box 155, Item 13)
    - “Boston Pops rolls 1 & 2” 8407001 V. 4 (16 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 155, Item 14)
    - “Boston Pops rolls 1A & 2A” 8407001 V. 5 (23 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 155, Item 15)
    - “Boston Pops rolls 3 & 4” 8407001 V. 6 (17 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 155, Item 16)
    - “Boston Pops rolls 5-7” 8407001 V.7 (17 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 155, Item 17)
    - China Tape #4, Beijing-Ethnic Nationalities College (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 1)
    - China Tape #5, Beijing Show #1 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 2)
    - China Tape #7, Beijing Show #3 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 3)
    - China Tape #9, Xian Show Tape #1 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 4)
    - China Tape #10, Xian Show Tape #2 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 5)
    - China Tape #11, Xian Show Tape 2 Shanxi Opera Dance Troupe (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 6)
    - China Tape #12, Xian Textile Mill & Kindergarten (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 7)
    - China #13 Xian Kindergarten, street scenes, free market (Less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 8)
    - China #14 Xian middle school (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 9)
    - China #15 Nanjing Tape #1 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 10)
    - China #16 Nanjing Tape #2 The Show (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 11)
    - China #17 Nanjing Tape #3 Jogging Sum Yat-Sen Mausoleum (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 12)
    - China #18 Nanjing Tape #4 Arts College Show (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 13)
    - China #19 Train to Wuxi Lake Taihu (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 14)
    - China #20 Dec 15, Wuxi streets canal silk (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 156, Item 15)
    - China #21 Wuxi Tape #2 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 1)
    - China #22 Shanghai Tape #1 Dec 17 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 2)
    - China #23 Shanghai Show Tape #1 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 3)
    - China #24 Shanghai Show Tape #2 (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 4)
    - China #25 Dec 18 Hua Choa Township (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 5)
    - China #26, 27, 28 Combined dub (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 6)
    - China #27 Dec 18 Childrens Palace show (less than 20 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 7)
    - A Common Beat (22 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 157, Item 8)
    - Communities of Peace (112 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 157, Item 9)
    - CTV Centro TV Vaticano, “Videre Petrum” (125 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 157, Item 10)
    - "The Dream Is Alive" 35th Anniversary Up with People in the World Today (9 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 157, Item 11)
    - Face to Face (65 minutes), undated; Betacam SP (Box 157, Item 12)
    - Face to Face tape 5A (65 minutes), undated; 1” Type C videotape (Box 158, Item 1)
    - Face to Face tape 5B (65 minutes), undated; 1” Type C videotape (Box 158, Item 2)
    - Face to Face tape 5C (65 minutes), undated; 1” Type C videotape (Box 158, Item 3)
    - Face to Face tape 5D, switched program tape (72 minutes), undated; 1” Type C videotape (Box 158, Item 4)
    - Face to Face tape 6D (66 minutes), undated; 1” Type C videotape (Box 158, Item 5)
    - Faces/ More than the Music video insert pieces without narration (6 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 1)
    - Gaff N.G. Master Mix (1st Mix) (18 minutes: 648 feet), undated; 16mm magnetic film (Box 159, Item 2)
    - Honeywell Concert Excerpts (49 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 3)
    - Japan: Chiba/Kumamoto (57 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 4)
    - Japan: Nagoya, Takamatsu, Tokyo (37 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 5)
    - Japan: Nara, Hiroshima, Niigata (57 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 6)
    - Jordan/Boston Pops Concert (18 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 159, Item 7)
    - Making of Super Bowl Spectacular with Ralph Colwell (8 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 1)
    - Mayor of Viseu sponsor a student Portugal (10 minutes), undated; Betacam SP Pal (Box 160, Item 2)
    - Mountain Bell special program with show footage (15 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 3)
    - National Symphony Orchestra, Constitution Hall (147 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 4)
    - “The New American” (58 minutes: 2088 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 160, Item 5)
    - Peace by Piece communities of Peace Program (10 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 6)
    - People’s Republic of China Room for Everyone (6 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 7)
    - Project Pride (6 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 8)
    - Project Pride training (120 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 9)
    - Project Pride, Video #1 (122 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 10)
    - Promotion The Up with People Story (20 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 11)
    - Ready for a New Century Part 1 (60 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 12)
    - Ready for a New Century Part 2 (33 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 13)
    - Roads music loop (60 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 160, Item 14)
    - San Xavier Mission, Tape #2 (17 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 160, Item 15)
    - Skin Deep (56 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 161, Item 1)
    - S.R. #3 Mag film (25 minutes: 900 feet), undated; 16mm magnetic film (Box 161, Item 2)
    - Steve Rokowski personal CBS special (60 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 161, Item 3)
    - “That American” (21 minutes: 749 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 161, Item 4)
    - “Tomorrow’s America” (27 minutes: 993 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 161, Item 5)
    - 25th Anniversary Denver Highlights (11 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (3 tapes) (Box 161, Item 6)
    - Up with Cox Heroes Program & UWP Concert (115 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 161, Item 7)
    - UWP at the Jerash Festival Jordan (6 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 161, Item 8)
    - UWP in China (5 minutes), undated; 1” Type C Videotape (Box 161, Item 9)
    - UWP in Italy A & C Rolls (Roll A output as JPG sequence; C Roll is title elements) (25 minutes: 925 feet), undated; 16mm film, positive, color, original (Box 162, Item 1)
    - UWP in Italy B-Roll (output as numbered JPG sequence) (25 minutes: 925 feet), undated; 16mm film, positive, color, original (Box 162, Item 2)
    - UWP in Italy, optical sound, faded print (25 minutes: 900 feet), undated; 16mm film, positive, color (Box 162, Item 3)
    - UWP in Italy, optical sound, faded print, short version (20 minutes: 780 feet), undated; 16mm film, positive, color (Box 162, Item 4)
    - UWP in the USSR with Mary Hart (11 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 162, Item 5)
    - UWP- Mexico (25 minutes: 900 feet), undated; 16mm film, positive, color (Box 163, Item 1)